[Music]
the focus was getting the integration of
the bhartiyaksa business uh done or
yes
we are very happy with the way the
processes work
[Music]
or if you see the impact of the business
uh icc lombard post this integration
has become the second largest insurer in
the country
uh in terms of uh post integration
integration happened in september post
integration uh most of the synergy
benefits on the revenue side
now we are focusing on the cost side and
scaling of the business now on the
scaling of the business
this quarter has been a very good
quarter for us in terms of top line
growth we've grown for the quarter in
line with the market but for the month
of march we have grown significantly
higher than the market
going ahead
a momentum
or
at least
[Music]
you know once we do that there'll be
some savings there also
the other thing is productivity increase
that though
no team
or business but well it can be not
necessarily having to add more manpower
so that is helping us in terms of
increasing manpower productivity uh in
terms of advertisement there are savings
so there are savings on the cost side
across board on the claim side we are
seeing some efficiencies or efficiencies
savings
but most of the savings that we are
seeing
some of it has already come in in the
year gone by uh in the last five six
months
next year we are expecting significant
more uh you know synergy benefits on the
operating cost side
is
integration of the bharti except
business and isa lombard business
we have taken another big step we have
been the first insurance company that
has moved it's all its core first large
insurance company which has moved its
all its core business core applications
to the cloud so we are now completely on
the cloud
this may again say we will have to now
see how we can leverage the cloud but
cloud gives us scalability flexibility
uh elasticity in terms of you know
increasing business fast and managing
cost you know in that sense
but it also gives us opportunity to do
more things on the digital ecosystem or
amount of focus try in terms of from the
customer perspective you know use
technology to build convenience both in
sourcing in service in engagement uh and
in claims so just a few examples uh you
know for example motor claims now of 80
of the claims are done through our
videos you know app through which you
can you know either the garage or
customer themselves can do a do a survey
with our support
uh
we are using artificial intelligence to
process health claims much faster about
sixty percent of our claims
uh the approval happens uh within about
uh you know few minutes compared to few
hours
uh similarly on the
on the digital side
there is a huge investment that we are
making on our mobile app the ielts take
care this may have teleconsultation tele
health video consultation
uh you know with a face scan you know on
the app there is a face scan feature
with your face scan you can get your
oxygen saturation levels your stress
levels your bp levels so these are you
know areas that we are investing in and
we believe these are very
um they can for the year gone by i can
tell you um
for us since we have a small share a
smaller share of health
uh we have had a 550 crore plus hit on
our pnl because of covet in the quarter
gone by that was about 27 crores
the only
you know positive development in our
opinion is that because of vaccination
because of more awareness um we don't
see
the risk in the same way that we saw in
wave two
so we are hopeful that agar wherefore
you know i we we all hope that it
doesn't
uh the hospitalization levels are less
other thing that we've seen is that for
mild uh illness you don't need to go to
hospital because we are providing tele
you know delhi uh you know health we are
providing home based care so on a
cashless basis if you inform us we will
provide to our network partners cashless
home uh you know home health care
service so that you don't have to go to
a hospital you can get treated for mild
uh you know illness at home
if the element is severe then you of
course we will take you to the hospital
like any service business particularly
in you know a you know financial
services business and in a business like
insurance scale has a tremendous
advantage uh
both in terms of investment that you can
do for technology i was talking about
the technology investment
in terms of the data that you have and
the analytics and the artificial
intelligence that you can you know
models that you can build
you know in terms of the cost advantage
of scale and these are the reasons that
you know if you if you have a large
efficient company just by being large
doesn't help
you have to leverage the advantage of
being large
and build better services and better
products for customers using all of
these capabilities that i talked about
if you do that you know market share
will definitely shift to the better
large place and that as a trend we
believe will happen for the next five
ten years